<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>愛</title>
    <link>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on 愛</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 11:13:55 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2023-01-28</title>
      <link>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2023-01-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 11:13:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2023-01-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi&#34;&gt;HI!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CSS, or Cascading Style Sheets, is a powerful styling language that can be used to create visually stunning designs and effects on websites and applications. One of the features of CSS that I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been exploring is the use of em units.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who may not be familiar, em units are a way to define the size of text or other elements in relation to the size of the font of the parent element. This allows for greater flexibility in designing responsive layouts, as the size of elements will automatically adjust based on the size of the font.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with using em units in my Waybar config, a status bar for Wayland compositors. By using em units, I can create designs that automatically adjust to the size of the font, making it easier to create visually pleasing layouts that look great on different screen sizes and resolutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what really caught my attention was the ability to use custom keyframes to create gradient animations in my waybar. This is a really cool feature that allows me to create animations that change the color of my status bar over time. It&amp;rsquo;s a really simple yet effective way to add a touch of personality and style to my setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an example of a gradient animation that I have been working on &amp;mdash;&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     &lt;img src=&#34;https://chiefdinkan.github.io/css.gif&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, I&amp;rsquo;ve found that using em units and custom keyframes in my Waybar config has opened up a whole new world of possibilities for customizing my setup and making it my own. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to continue experimenting with different styles and effects, and to see what other cool things I can come up with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also need to learn eww asap because I been lazy for too long.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022-12-02</title>
      <link>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2022-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 23:07:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2022-12-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;namaskaram-&#34;&gt;Namaskaram 🙏&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was tasked to create a CNN for a project in a hackathon named &amp;ldquo;AITHON&amp;rdquo; conducted by the IEEE club in my college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first step in creating a CNN for a project in a hackathon is to define the problem. What is the goal of the project? What data is available? What is the desired outcome? Once the problem is clearly defined, the next step is to develop a strategy for building the CNN. This includes selecting the appropriate architecture, layers, and hyperparameters. Additionally, the data should be preprocessed and split into training, validation, and testing sets. After the CNN is built, it should be tested and evaluated to ensure it is performing as expected. Finally, the model should be deployed and used to generate predictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-steps-i-followed-were&#34;&gt;The steps I followed were:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collect and preprocess the data: I gathered images of people with different emotions and preprocessed them to ensure they were of the same size and format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create the CNN architecture: I used a convolutional neural network (CNN) architecture with multiple layers, including convolutional, pooling, and fully connected layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Train the model: I used the training data to train the model, adjusting the hyperparameters to optimize the model’s performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test the model: I tested the model on the validation data to evaluate its performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deploy the model: I deployed the model to a web application and used it to generate predictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tools I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the development of the CNN are jupyter notebook and google colab to write the code, tensorflow and keras for building the model, opencv for preprocessing the data, and matplotlib for visualizing the results.
Also, I used a library called sklearn for splitting the data into training, validation, and testing sets, and for optimizing the hyperparameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;why-sklearnhttpsgithubcomscikit-learnscikit-learn&#34;&gt;why &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/scikit-learn/scikit-learn&#34;&gt;sklearn&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sklearn is a powerful library for machine learning that provides a wide range of tools for data preprocessing, model building, and model evaluation. It is particularly useful for splitting data into training, validation, and testing sets, as well as for optimizing hyperparameters. Additionally, it provides a range of metrics for evaluating the performance of a model.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;why-kerashttpsgithubcomkeras-teamkeras&#34;&gt;why &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/keras-team/keras&#34;&gt;keras&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keras is a high-level API for building and training deep learning models. It is easy to use and provides a range of tools for building complex models. Additionally, it is compatible with a variety of backends, including TensorFlow, which makes it a great choice for building CNNs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Would probably publish my  model on a platform such as Kaggle or GitHub and make it available to the public soon as  I am free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And this Entire blog was created using openai&amp;rsquo;s GPT-3 model text-davinci-003 using the openai API and python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to demonstrate the capabilities of OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-3 model and how it can be used to generate text. GPT-3 is a powerful language model that can generate text based on a prompt. By using the OpenAI API and Python, I was able to generate this blog post with minimal effort.(This was also written by the ai. sed :| )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ig Ai was kool after all. Now I need to learn more about this.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022-11-13</title>
      <link>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2022-10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 11:35:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefdinkan.github.io/blog/2022-10-13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been diving deeper into the world of Hugo lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a really cool experience.
The ability to quickly create a static website using markdown and pre-designed themes makes it a breeze to put together a site without too much hassle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I&amp;rsquo;ve run into a few issues along the way. For example, getting a Freenom domain has been a bit more complicated than I expected.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also had some trouble with the latest update to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Alexays/Waybar&#34;&gt;Waybar&lt;/a&gt;, which ended up messing with my style.css and causing a few headaches.
But, I was able to fix it by downgrading some dependencies and using the Waybar-Hyprland-git package.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hyprwm/Hyprland&#34;&gt;Hyprland&lt;/a&gt; as my daily driver for the past two months and it&amp;rsquo;s been a really pleasant experience.
It&amp;rsquo;s not without its bugs, but I&amp;rsquo;m confident that they&amp;rsquo;ll be ironed out in the future.
This is how my Desktop looks now &amp;ndash;&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://chiefdinkan.github.io/sed.png&#34; alt=&#34;desk&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I Need to learn &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/elkowar/eww&#34;&gt;eww&lt;/a&gt; and do something cool with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thats all for today ig.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
